Guide to the Shanghai American School Records: the Phoebe White Wentworth Collection of Shanghai American School History and Memorabilia
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Shanghai American School Alumni Association, Series II
  - Alumni/ae Records, 1924-1997, n.d.
    - Original collection
      - American Schools in China- reunion information
        - General information- Asilomar, CA, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 197)
        - General information and biographies- Monterey, CA, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 198)
        - General information and letters- Hershey, PA, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 199)
        - Biographies, Hershey, PA, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 200)
        - General information- Santa Rosa, CA, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 201)
        - General information- San Diego, CA, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 202)
        - Biographies, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 203)
      - Miscellaneous alumni/ae records
        - "Old China hands: a roster", 1945 (Box 22, Folder 204)
        - List of "Old School" Alumni and SAS married couples, various dates (Box 22, Folder 204-A)
        - Unofficial alumni directory by Paul Mcginnis, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 205)
        - Directory of post-war students and faculty, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 206)
        - News clippings about various SAS alumni/ae (Box 22, Folder 207)
        - Works by or about alumni/ae (Box 22, Folder 208)
        - Alumni Association dues notice, 1993,1995 (Box 22, Folder 209)
    - Addendum - 2010
      - Miscellaneous records related to SAS graduates including letters, member lists, trips to China, biographies, film information, 1975-2001 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Membership directory, 1991 March (Box 29, Folder 49)
      - Membership directory, 1992 June (Box 29, Folder 50)
      - Membership directory, 1994, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 51)
      - Membership directory, 1999 May (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Addendum - 2011
      - Autobiography excerpts - Myles H. Walburn, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Autobiography - Edward F. Pilley, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Diary of K. Pilley (mother of Edward), 1947-1948 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Letters - Maggie Naismith, 1946-1948 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Memorabilia, photos - Patricia P. Emery, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Household accounts - Avent family, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Reunion information
    - Original collection
      - Biographies and letters, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 172)
      - General information- Washington D.C., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 173)
      - "Who's Who" - Alexandria, VA, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 174)
      - Reunion booklet- Alexandria, VA, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 175)
      - Songs and games, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 176)
      - Reunion booklet, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 177)
      - Biographies - Williamsburg, VA, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 178)
      - "Memories of the 40th Reunion of post-war Faculty and Students", 1989 (Box 19, Folder 179)
      - Biographies- Mendenhall, PA, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 180)
      - General information- Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 181)
      - General information- Chadd's Ford, PA, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 182)
      - Biographies- Chadd's Ford, PA, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 183)
      - Kaleidoscope II (memory album), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 184)
      - Biographies and selected correspondence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 185)
      - Letter concerning Vienna, Va. reunion, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 186)
      - General information and Letters- Kansas City, KS, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 187)
      - Letters, biographies and class history- Arlington, VA, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 188)
      - General information and letters- Tucson, AZ, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 189)
      - Letters, biographies and class histories- Indianapolis, IN, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 190)
      - General information- Williamsburg, VA, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 191)
      - General information- Southwest Harbor, ME, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 192)
      - General information- Southwest Harbor, ME, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 193)
      - Photographs- Southwest Harbor, ME, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 194)
      - Letters- Southwest Harbor, ME, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 195-196)
      - General Information-Sarasota, FL, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 196-A)
      - Misc. Photos of SAS-ites, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 196-B)
    - Addendum - 2010
      - Correspondence planning 20th reunion of class of 1949 in Washington, DC, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - Alexandria, VA - 1980 Jun 15 (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - 40th Reunion - Culver City, CA - 1989 Oct 6-8 (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - Directory Post-war students and faculty (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - China American Schools reunion - San Diego, CA - 1991 Mar 15-17 (Box 30, Folder 57-59)
      - 50th reunion, class of 1941 - Atlanta, GA - 1991 Oct 15-20 (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - Biographical sketches, class of 1941 (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - 80th anniversary of SAS founding - 1992 Sep 12 (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - Respected Elders Reunion - classes of 1918-1933 - Kansas City - 1992 Oct 2-4 (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - 50th reunion - classes of 1942,1943 - Arlington, VA - 1993 May 21-23 (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - Follow-up from reunion, 1993 Jun - Oct (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - Letters and biographies - classes of 1942, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - 45th Reunion - Post-war students and faculty - Indianapolis, IN - 1994 Jun 18 (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - All China American Schools Reunion - Williamsburg, VA - 1994 Oct 30- Nov 1 (Box 30, Folder 68, 69)
      - 60th Reunion, class of 1937 - assisted by classes of 1938, 1942, 1943 - Sarasota, FL - 1997 Sep 28-30 (Box 31, Folder 70, 71)
      - 60th Reunion, class of 1940 - bound booklet including biographices, photos, memories - Rosslyn, VA - 2000 Oct (Box 31, Folder 72)
      - Post-war SAS Reunion - Gatlinburg, TN - 2002 Oct 18-20 (Box 31, Folder 73)
      - All SAS Reunion - host classes 1941, 1942, 1943 - Orlando, FL - 2003 Apr 24-27 (Box 31, Folder 74)
      - All SAS Reunion - Bellingham, WA - 2005 Sep 15-18 (Box 31, Folder 75)
  - Collected material
    - Added in 2010
      - Miscellaneous programs, maps, music (Box 31, Folder 76)
      - Book: The Observatory of Zi-Ka-Wei (Box 31, Folder 77)
    - Added in 2011
      - Reports on the Nanking Affair, 1927 Mar (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Audio-visual material
    - Added in 2010
      - Photographs from reunions and trips (Box 31, Folder 78)
      - VHS cassette - 2003 reunion in TN (See also VHS film footage related to Shanghai American School in Stannard papers, Record Group No. 8), 2004 (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Added in 2011
      - VHS tapes of SAS reunions, 1989, 1994, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 19-22)
      - DVD of SAS reunion, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Added in 2015
      - Photographs from reunions (Box 34, Folder 7)